http://www.amca.uk.com/privacy-policy

Enter Event / 1 Day Licence
FIXTURES
Motocross FixturesScrambles FixturesTrials FixturesCycle Trials FixturesEnduro Fixtures
MENU
HomeMotocross Start Motocross RacingApply for a LicenceFixturesBritish Championships2020 MediaEuropean Championships2020 Champions2019 ChampionsChampionship GalleriesMotocross Groups/Regional ChampionshipsMotocross Fixtures DownloadReports & ResultsMember BenefitsNewsFormsFAQsScrambles Start Scrambles RacingApply for a LicenceFixtures/Online EntryFixtures/Download Entry FormsBritish Classic ChampionshipAMCA UK Evo ChampionshipRace Number CheckReports & ResultsNewsFAQsOrder Scrambling & Trials YearbookTrials Start TrialsStart Cycle TrialsApply for a LicenceFixturesMidland Modern TrialsReports & ResultsNewsFAQsEnduro Start EnduroApply for a LicenceFixturesChampionshipsReports & ResultsNewsFAQsBeach Racing Weymouth Beach RaceSkegness Beach RaceAbout About the AMCALandownersAMCA LandInsuranceGeneral FAQsTrophiesEquipmentMinutesRulebooksGDPRNews Motocross NewsScrambles NewsTrials NewsEnduro NewsGeneral NewsContactClubs Affiliate as a ClubClub FormsFind Your ClubYamaha MX Experience
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how the Amateur Motor Cycle Association Limited (AMCA) uses and protects any information that you give AMCA when you use this website or the Sport80 online booking system.
AMCA is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
AMCA may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 8th May 2018.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name and date of birth/age;
contact information including email address;
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests;
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping;
We may use the information to improve our products and services;
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided;
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added, and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Visitors to our websites
When someone visits www.amca.uk.com we use a third party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make, or allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
The collection or use of your personal information can be restricted in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that indicates you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes and make sure it is unchecked;
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you, please write to Data Protection Officer, The Amateur Motor Cycle Association Ltd, Hyland House, Navigation Way, Mill Park, Cannock, WS11 7XU.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Google Analytics
Google Analytics uses cookies to collect information about how visitors use our site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. We use Google Analytics information to understand how our web site is performing and to help us improve the site. These are Category 2 cookies.
Online Services
Follow this link to log into your secure online account to update your details, renew your licence, and enter events.
Login and Enter Events
How can I start?
This all depends on what discipline you want to start with – some require you to take a licence whilst others are more flexible and allow you to turn up and ride. Once you have opted for a discipline, see the FAQ for more tailored questions.
What is the difference between motocross, enduro, and trials?
These are all different disciplines the AMCA caters for, along with much more. Motocross is fast paced, short races over both natural and man-made terrain with 36 riders going into a first corner. Enduro is more long distance, long duration events, usually through woodland. Trials is slow paced, technical, balance based over challenging short course with the object to go through without putting your foot on the floor.
How old do I have to be?
The AMCA accepts riders from the age of 6 for trials, 7 for motocross, 11 for enduro and supermoto, and 16 for classic scrambles.
VIEW MORE FAQS
